What the heck!
這算什麼神器
How come the sacred treasure lost its power so quickly?
竟然這麼快就失去效果
Princess Iris.
愛麗絲殿下
Now is not the time to change back!
別在這種節骨眼換回來啦
(Episode 6: Farewell to the Good Life) Hey, Kazuma.
(第6集 向美好的生活說再見) 和真
-Yes. I'm Kazuma. -You treat me like an idiot all the time.
-平常你總是把我當成笨蛋 -是 我是和真
I can finally say it out now.
現在我終於能說了
You are a super-duper idiot, aren't you?
和真先生是無敵大笨蛋吧
I'm not!
才不是
I subconsciously believe
我走在城堡裡的時候
that I am someone who will be forgiven for anything
會有很多人對我點頭哈腰
because so many people bow
讓我不自覺以為
and nod to me when I walk in the castle.
自己是做什麼都會被原諒的人
You really are an idiot, aren't you?
你果然是笨蛋吧
Give it some more serious thought!
給我認真一點反省
I didn't expect even Iris to be this angry.
沒想到連愛麗絲都那麼生氣
This is killing me.
哥哥活不下去了
Is all he does just talk the talk?
他就是只會耍嘴皮的人嗎
Geez.
真是的
Why would Lady Dustiness
達斯堤尼斯大人
team up with someone like that?
為什麼要和那樣的人當夥伴
Exactly.
就是啊
Princess Iris has already gone back to her room.
愛麗絲殿下先去休息了
I-I see.
這…這樣啊
Now it's finally time to say goodbye.
這下子終於要說再見了啊
Enjoy the victory feast today.
今天你就好好享受慶功宴吧
That is, if you have the courage to enjoy it.
前提是你有膽量享受的話
Damn it.
可惡
What's with that woman?
那個女人是怎樣啊
She kept being sarcastic all the way through.
直到最後一刻都在挖苦我
Of course, I was at fault too.
當然我也有錯
It's more accurate to say it was all my fault.
不如說都是我的錯
But I really want to stay in the castle longer!
但我好想在城堡待久一點
My answer will always be the same, no matter how many times you come.
不管妳來幾遍 我的回答都一樣
Alright, alright, don't say that.
好啦好啦 別這麼說嘛
Let me tell you.
我就告訴妳吧
The castle contains a sacred treasure with the ability to swap bodies.
城堡裡有能交換身體的神器
I don't think that is dangerous, though.
但我認為那種東西沒有危險
You can't go back
那個東西
to the original state
如果交換身體的期間
if the other one dies
其中一個人死掉
during the body swap, you know?
就無法恢復原狀喔
What?
什麼
Depending on how it is used,
那是能根據使用方式
that thing has the power to give eternal life.
得到永恆生命的超強物品
If your body gets old,
如果自己的身體衰老了
just swap it with someone young and healthy and kill them.
只要和年輕又健康的人交換身體
And that is it.
再殺掉對方就行了
This is a big problem.
這可不是鬧著玩的
Those influential people need to know this immediately…
必須趕快告訴那些大人物
I think it would be wiser if you didn't.
我勸你還是別這麼做比較好
Do you know what those who discover the sacred treasure's power
你知道得知神器力量的人們
would do with it?
會拿它怎麼辦嗎
Nobles from all over the country
我敢斷言
will surely come to steal the sacred treasure, I dare say it.
全國的貴族都會來搶神器
Because of eternal life?
因為永恆的生命嗎
I am only disclosing this to you
我會告訴你這些
because I have faith that you will not abuse it.
是因為我覺得你不會拿它來做壞事
Huh?
奇怪
What makes her trust me so much?
這傢伙意外地很相信我嗎
Hey.
我說
Were you not tasked with accompanying the princess on her playdate?
你是負責陪王女殿下玩的人吧
Would you like to play with the princess now?
要不要現在去找王女殿下玩啊
What?
什麼
Very good, very good.
很好很好
This victory feast is rocking!
大家都在戰勝慶功宴玩得很嗨
So the guard is very lax.
所以戒備很鬆懈
Indeed.
的確
Hey.
喂
What is that get-up of yours?
那是什麼打扮啊
Isn't it unfair that only you are hiding who you are?
只有妳一個人隱藏身分太奸詐了吧
I obtained it from a suspicious clerk
這是從某個魔法道具店裡的
at a specific magical item store.
可疑店員手上得到的
I heard it's a best-selling product.
聽說是暢銷商品喔
So, errand boy,
那麼 跑腿小弟
are you ready?
你做好心理準備了嗎
I am always ready.
我隨時都可以出發喔
Boss.
老大
Please, don't call me boss.
拜託你別叫我老大啦
Then do not call me errand boy.
那妳也不要叫我跑腿小弟
In the name of a chivalrous thief,
在這座王都以義賊的名義
I am the one making a big name in this royal capital.
聲名大噪的人可是我耶
How about we play a game of rock-paper-scissors to decide?
那就跟我猜拳決勝負怎麼樣
Alright, let's play rock-paper-scissors.
好啊 來猜拳吧
(Konosuba) Ready?
我要出囉
Rock, paper…
剪刀石頭…
Assistant.
助手小弟
The princess is right here, correct?
王女殿下就在這裡對吧
Yes, chief.
對 首領
I lost at rock-paper-scissors for the first time in my life.
我有生以來第一次猜拳輸了
Despite being very skilled,
就算本克莉絲小姐再厲害
I am facing such a height…
面對這種高度也…
Snipe.
狙擊
Having an assistant is really handy.
助手小弟真方便
So far, everything has gone smoothly.
到目前為止都很順利
Shh.
噓
Chief, I've sensed the enemy.
首領 我感應到敵人了
Hey, Assistant.
喂 助手小弟
We have used the lurk.
我們都使用潛伏技能了
You don't need to stand so close.
用不著貼這麼近吧
We mustn't be careless, Chief.
千萬不能大意 首領
Get closer a bit.
再貼近一起
Come on, hurry up!
來 快點快點
Hey, too close!
喂 太近了
This is to protect world peace.
這也是為了守護世界和平
You have to endure it.
妳要忍耐
Please endure it.
請妳忍耐
Hey!
喂
You will be punished by the Goddess Eris when the time comes.
你到時候會受到艾莉絲女神的天譴
It's thieves!
是盜賊
Thieves have appeared!
盜賊出現了
Alert! Alert!
來人啊 來人啊
It is all because you yelled out of the blue!
都怪首領突然大叫
I need to talk to you later!
我晚點有很多話要跟你說
It is not the time to argue.
現在不是吵架的時候
You're not qualified to say that.
你沒資格這麼說
Don't let them get up there!
別讓他們上去
Princess Iris is on the top floor.
愛麗絲殿下在最頂樓
Create Water.
Create Water
Freeze.
Freeze
Stop right there!
站住
Having an assistant is very convenient.
助手小弟真的很方便呢
Don't just talk the talk.
別光說不練
Chief, you should help out too.
拜託首領也幫幫忙啦
Okay.
好
I'll let you witness the chief's power.
我就讓你看看首領的實力吧
Wire Trap!
Wire Trap
You should use this move sooner.
這種招式拜託妳早點用啦
All right, this will buy us some time.
好了 這樣就能拖一點時間
I didn't realize you'd cut yourselves off.
沒想到你們會自己斷了退路
Damned thief.
可惡的盜賊
You won't be able to escape now.
你們現在休想逃走了
This is not good.
這下子不妙啊
That's it!
就是那個
Let us get away from that.
我們從那裡逃出去吧
No, wait a minute.
不 等一下
It should be settled today.
我希望能在今天想辦法解決
Because tomorrow I have to leave the royal capital.
因為我明天就要被趕出王都了
Do you normally work this hard?
你是會這麼努力的類型嗎
Right.
對喔
Am I such a passionate character?
我是這麼熱血的角色嗎
Calm down.
冷靜點
I should be a colder man.
我應該是更冷酷的男人
Correct.
沒錯
Once I get back to Axel,
我只要回到阿克塞爾
I can have fun every day.
就能每天玩樂過生活
That's the situation here.
這裡的情況就是這樣
I really can't focus on my studies.
實在沒辦法專注在課業上
I want you to play this game with me today.
我希望你今天陪我玩這個遊戲
I have never met anyone like you before.
我第一次遇到你這樣的人
Everyone loves and cherishes you,
受到大家的愛護
and you are brave,
什麼都不怕
rude, and outspoken.
沒禮貌又直言不諱
Hey!
喂
I'm not asking what you dislike about me,
我不是在問妳討厭我什麼地方
Yeah, I'm telling you the reasons I like you.
嗯 我正在說喜歡你的理由喔
Chief, I…
首領 我…
Okay, now it is time for me to impress you.
現在要拿出真本事了
Assistant?
助手小弟?
Cut the chatter.
少說廢話
What?
什麼
What skill is that, Assistant?
助手小弟 那個技能是什麼
That's exactly why I kept it a secret.
就是因為這樣我才保密
Great, this is so great!
太棒了 太棒了
For some reason, I'm in great condition!
不知為何我的狀況超棒
My magic has gotten stronger, and my blood flow has gotten better.
魔力提高 血液循環變好
My skin also looks great.
肌膚也很有光澤
Tonight I will show you what I am really capable of.
今晚我要讓你們見識我的真本事
The Silver-Haired Thieves are coming!
銀髮盜賊團要通過了
Move out of the way
如果不想吃苦頭的話
if you do not want to suffer!
就讓路吧
This guy is very strong.
這傢伙好強
Despite wearing a strange mask.
明明戴著奇怪的面具
Lightning.
Lightning
Skill Bind.
Skill Bind
What?
什麼
The Silver-Haired Thieves sound terrible.
銀髮盜賊團太糟了啦
You should just be the chief
由你來當首領就好
and change it to something like the Masked Thieves.
改成面具盜賊團之類的
I refuse.
我拒絕
That makes me sound like the mastermind.
聽起來我才是主謀一樣
Who would like that?
誰喜歡啊
I don't like it either.
我也不喜歡啊
Miss Claire…
克萊兒小姐…
It seems like you've encountered formidable enemies.
妳們好像遇上強敵了啊
I, Swordsmanship Master,
那個假面男
will catch that man in the mask.
就由我這個劍術大師捉拿
Miss Claire…
克萊兒小姐…
This young man with silver hair is yours to handle.
那位銀髮少年就交給妳對付
Hey, Assistant.
喂 助手小弟
Do I really look that much like a boy?
我看起來這麼像男生嗎
It must be due to your flat chest.
是因為身材平板的關係吧
Pull yourself together.
打起精神來
What follows is the important part.
接下來才是重頭戲
I am going to take his Cursed Sword.
我要搶走他的魔劍…
That action looks like Steal.
看那個動作是Steal吧
Sadly,
很遺憾
after losing to a certain person,
我輸給某個男人後
I thought of a way to beat Steal.
就想出對付Steal的策略了
Steal,
Steal
It's no use.
沒用的
Wha--
什…
That's just a distraction.
那只是障眼法
Freeze.
Freeze
Then…
接著
What?
什麼
Create Water.
Create Water
Mr. Mitsurugi!
御劍先生
Who would go up against a Swordsmanship Master face-to-face?
誰會和劍術大師正面對抗啊
We must not underestimate the enemy.
不能大意輕敵
Is this ill will?
這就是惡意嗎
Delicious.
真美味
This is so delicious.
真是太美味了
You jerk!
你這傢伙
Dodge.
我閃
You should take care of that man right away.
妳最好馬上照顧那個男人
Mr. Mitsurugi!
御劍先生
Rain.
蕾茵
Quickly use magic to heal.
快點使用恢復魔法
I-I will use it right away.
我…我馬上用
Hurry, Chief.
快走 首領
Don't let them escape.
別讓他們逃走
Princess Iris is just up ahead.
愛麗絲殿下就在那前面
Come quickly! Someone come!
快來人啊 快來人啊
Ahead is Iris's room.
前面就是愛麗絲的房間
Understood, Assistant.
知道了 助手小弟
Great, this is so great!
太棒了 太棒了
This is just so great!
真是太棒了
This is it, intruder.
到此為止了 入侵者
It is my duty to defend the people,
守護人民 守護國家
the country,
還有守護王族
and the royal family…
是我的…
What do we do, Assistant?
怎…怎麼辦 助手小弟
Hey, jerk! Don't close the door!
喂 混蛋 別關門
What on earth are you up to?
你們到底有什麼目的
Intruder.
入侵者
Impressive that you've made it here.
虧你們能來到這裡
I am a royal who descended from heroes
我也是繼承勇者之血
and has the power to strengthen my position.
用這個力量鞏固地位的王族之一
I stake this heirloom royal ring…
我賭上這枚代代相傳的王族戒指…
Get out of the way.
讓開
Leave these petty thieves to me…
區區一兩個小賊就由我…
S-So cool.
好…好帥喔
What to do, Darkness?
怎麼辦 達克妮絲
This chivalrous thief has excellent taste.
這個義賊的品味真好
He is even wearing a cool mask
居然戴著這麼帥的面具
and dressed entirely in black.
還穿著一身黑衣
What is your team's name?
你們叫什麼
Is the name decided?
盜賊團的名字決定了嗎
Bind.
Bind
So cool.
好帥
Great.
好棒
Sacred Break Spell.
Sacred Break Spell
I am sorry
很遺憾
that running into me here means you have lost your luck.
我在這裡算你們運氣不好
I have no idea why you came here,
雖然不知道你們來這裡要幹嘛
but I will get
但只要抓到你們
the expensive bubble wine again if I catch you.
一定就能再得到高級的泡泡酒
Alright, surrender now.
好了 乖乖被抓吧
This guy…
這傢伙…
Darkness, now is the time!
達克妮絲 就是現在
Why Megumin has lost all her cool?
惠惠不知道為什麼變成窩囊廢了
We can only rely on you now.
我們現在只能靠妳了
Okay.
好
Chief.
首領
We'll try to get through and use Steal.
我們想辦法穿過去使出Steal
You plan to steal the sacred treasure, don't you?
你打算偷走神器吧
But your Steal…
可是你的Steal…
Are you going to say it'll steal underwear?
妳想說會偷走內褲嗎
Yeah.
嗯
Princess Iris!
愛麗絲殿下
Despicable fellow!
卑鄙的傢伙
How dare you use such means?
竟敢使用那種手段
Lord Dustiness!
達斯堤尼斯卿
Let's attack them from both sides!
我們夾擊他們
I am going to give it
看我使出渾身解數的
-Chief. -my all!
-首領 -一記
H-Horizontal slash!
橫…橫砍
That's why you're a useless cross knight.
就是這樣 妳才會是沒用的十字騎士
Princess Iris!
愛麗絲殿下
Now is the time!
就是現在
Steal.
Steal
Good job, Assistant.
很好 助手小弟
We're going to jump down from here.
我們要從這裡跳下去
My necklace!
我的項鍊被…
Even though I do not know what it is,
雖然不知道那是什麼東西
I can't let you take it away.
但我不能就這樣讓你們帶走
Up until the very end, that guy…
那傢伙 直到最後一刻
Seal.
封印
All jerks!
都是混蛋
S-So cool.
好…好帥喔
Calm down, calm down.
冷靜點 冷靜點啊
It's splitting, it's splitting!
要裂開了 要裂開了
My head is splitting!
我的頭要裂開了
I'm just being instigated.
我只是被唆使了
The mastermind is Chris!
主謀是克莉絲啦
You! Damn you!
你…你這傢伙真是…
That hurts.
好痛
You said the reason for making a fuss
妳說引發騷動的目的
is to get back a dangerous sacred treasure?
是為了收回危險的神器?
Why did not you tell me from the start?
為什麼不一開始就跟我說
It must have been very hard for you
要是被妳發現助手小弟和我串通
if you found out that he and I were working together.
我想妳的立場應該會很為難
That hurts!
好痛
Hey, you are not supposed to talk, okay?
喂喂 不准說喔
Geez.
真是的
Is there anything else you're hiding?
你們還有其他隱瞞的事嗎
It seems there is.
看來有啊
What's this?
這是…
Because working together increases the chances of success.
因為兩個人一起做成功率較高
Why do your Steal
你的Steal
keep stealing things that you shouldn't?
為什麼老是偷走不能偷的東西
It's not underwear this time.
這次又不是內褲
That's not the issue here.
問題不在這裡
Listen carefully, Kazuma.
聽好了 和真
You must never lose this ring.
你絕對不能弄丟這枚戒指喔
And don't let anyone find out about it.
然後別被任何人發現
Take it with you to the grave.
帶著它進墳墓
Hey, don't be like that.
喂 別這樣
As this is a very important item,
既然是這麼重要的東西
I will simply say that I found it nearby
我就說是在附近撿到的
and am now going to return it.
現在就拿去還吧
Idiot!
蠢貨
That hurts!
好痛
It is something that should be given to a future spouse
這是只有決定婚約者的時候 才能拿下來
and can only be taken off when an engagement is confirmed.
交給要成為自己伴侶的東西
But to think that it was stolen by thieves
但是它卻被盜賊搶走
and found by adventurers nearby?
還被附近的冒險者撿到
They would probably kill you to silence you
就算你好心送回去
even if you returned it.
也會被殺掉滅口吧
What does that mean? That's terrifying.
什麼意思 好可怕
Princess Iris has always worn this ring on her hand,
這是愛麗絲殿下一直戴在手上
and she really cares about it.
非常重視的戒指
Whatever happens,
不管發生什麼事
you have to keep it with you at all times
你都必須隨身帶著
and not let anyone see it.
別讓任何人看到它
I had no idea that necklace was so dangerous.
沒想到那條項鍊是這麼危險的東西
Good job, Lord Dustiness.
這次辛苦妳了 達斯堤尼斯卿
Thank you.
是
Speaking of which,
話說回來
you were of no use that night either.
你在那天晚上也沒派上任何用場呢
Could they
難道說
have been trying to help me?
那兩個人是為了救我才會…
If so,
如果是這樣
the thief who is said to be out there
傳聞中的盜賊
would really be a chivalrous thief.
就真的是正義的義賊了呢
How can that be possible?
怎麼可能
But if that is true,
不過 如果真的是這樣
I have to say they are pretty cool.
我不得不說他們很了不起
Huh?
咦咦
Are you talking about the person wearing the mask?
妳是說那個戴面具的人嗎
He's really cool, isn't he?
真的很帥吧
I was drawn to that mask
那個面具和黑色裝扮
and the black clothes.
非常打動我的心
If I see him again,
下次再見到他
I will definitely beg for an autograph.
我一定要跟他要簽名
Oh no, what should I do?
糟糕 怎麼辦
I wish I could brag to everyone that that is me.
好想跟大家炫耀其實那個人就是我
What's wrong, Kazuma?
和真你怎麼了
You've been giggling all the time. It's kind of disgusting, you know.
一直在偷笑 感覺很噁心耶
What exactly are you laughing about?
就是啊 你在偷笑什麼
The chivalrous thief
那個義賊
looks really handsome.
真的很帥呢
Given the circumstances,
看這個情況
she surely could not have guessed who the thief was, could she?
她該不會已經察覺盜賊是誰了吧
Their actions suggest
那兩個人一定是擔心我
that they are concerned about me.
才會採取那樣的行動
I might have fallen for that chivalrous thief.
我說不定喜歡上那位義賊了
Okay.
好
I'll reveal my identity then.
我表明身分吧
W-What's the matter, Kazuma?
怎…怎麼了 和真
-Why did you suddenly stand up? -What are you doing?
-妳幹嘛啦 -為什麼突然站起來
Do you need to pee? Do you need to pee?
是想小便嗎 是想小便嗎
-You're such a pain. -Do you want to see me pee?
-妳想看嗎 -真拿你沒辦法
-I am very sorry. -Okay.
-好啊 -非常抱歉
-I'll get this rude guy out of here right away. -I'll just pee right here for you to see.
-我就在這裡小便給妳看 -我馬上把這個無禮的傢伙趕出去
Hey, quickly let go.
喂 快點放開那隻手
Otherwise, I'll use Drain Touch.
不然我就用Drain Touch
That chief
不知道
with the silver hair has me wondering
他現在在哪裡做什麼呢
about him and his whereabouts.
那位銀髮的首領先生
It makes me a little sad to leave.
雖然有點依依不捨
Older brother.
兄長大人
I have a wish.
我有一個願望
I have something to say
在您說出那個願望之前
before you bring up that wish.
我有話要說
This person has defeated many Leaders of the Devil King's Army.
這個人打敗了許多魔王軍幹部
Eventually,
然後
he might beat the Devil King.
他總有一天說不定會打敗魔王
Even though it is hard to do
雖然這是非常困難
and not very likely to happen.
不容易達成的事
Could you kindly offer some words of encouragement to him,
能不能請您對勇於挑戰困難的他
who is courageous enough to face the challenges head-on?
說些勉勵的話呢
What is she talking about now?
這傢伙 突然間胡說什麼啊
Defeat the Devil King?
打敗魔王?
Really?
真的嗎
Are you really going to defeat the Devil King?
兄長大人真的要打敗魔王嗎
How could that possi--
那怎麼可能…啊
Well. If there is a chance, it appears like a good idea to go
這…這個嘛 如果有機會的話
and subdue the Devil King.
去討伐魔王似乎也不錯
Older brother, you can surely do it!
兄長大人一定能辦到
Please do your best to repel the Devil King!
請你努力擊退魔王
You keep calling him "older brother."
開口閉口都是兄長大人
Stop calling him that.
妳不要再這樣稱呼他了
You have your own real brother, right?
妳有真正的兄長大人吧
Why don't you go and flirt with him?
去跟他打情罵俏不就好了
One day, I will personally put an end to the Devil King.
總有一天我會親手葬送魔王
Kazuma doesn't need to action.
根本不需要和真出馬
He is older brother.
兄長大人就是兄長大人
What is wrong with calling him
我稱兄長大人為兄長大人
"older brother"?
哪裡錯了
Besides, there's no point in you defeating the Devil King.
而且妳打敗魔王根本沒意義
I hope that older brother will defeat the Devil King.
我是希望兄長大人打敗魔王
I just told you not to call him that!
我才剛叫妳不要說
And yet you keep calling him "older brother"!
妳就一直喊兄長大人
Are you challenging me?
難道是在對我挑釁嗎
D-Do you want to fight?
要…要打架嗎
The royal family is very strong, you know.
王族可是很強的喔
-Hey, stop it, Megumin! -What are you talking about?
-喂 惠惠 別鬧了 -妳說什麼
-Clearly, you and Princess Iris -Even the royal family would not be
-妳昨天明明才不知不覺 -在我的爆裂魔法面前
-became closer yesterday. -able to stop my explosion magic!
-和愛麗絲殿下感情變好了 -就算是王族也束手無策
- Princess Iris, please calm down. -Fine, experience it for yourself then.
-愛麗絲殿下 請您冷靜點 -好啊 妳就親自體會看看吧
-You clearly haven't fought with anyone else. -My Exterion is also very strong, okay?
-您明明沒有跟別人打過架 -我的Exterion也很強好嗎
So what?
所以呢
What is your wish?
妳的願望是什麼
Go ahead and say it.
儘管說吧
My wish…
我的願望…
My wish is…
我的願望是…
The outcome of our game has not been decided yet.
我們的遊戲還沒有分出勝負
Please play with me again sometime.
請您有機會再跟我比賽吧
Hey, shut up!
喂 吵死了
The neighbors would be irritated.
你會吵到左鄰右舍
Go yell in the suburbs.
要叫就到郊外去叫
Are you kidding me?
開什麼玩笑
I can't believe you would step in at that critical juncture.
竟然在緊要關頭妨礙我
-If you had not brought up the Devil King, -Next, please sign this for me.
-接著是請幫我簽名 -要是妳沒有提什麼魔王
Iris might have wished for something else.
愛麗絲應該會許別的願望
"I want to be with older brother."
我想和兄長大人在一起
"I want to date older brother."
我想和兄長大人交往
"I want to sleep with older brother."
我想和兄長大人一起睡之類的
How is that possible?
那怎麼可能啊
By the way, are you really certain
再說你有自信在短短一星期內
that you can win over a girl to this degree in only a week?
就讓異性喜歡你到這種程度嗎
You must confront the reality.
要好好認清現實
Do not bring me back to reality all of a sudden.
不要突然把我拉回現實
I don't want to hear this kind of grandstanding.
我不想聽這種冠冕堂皇的話
Just let me dream a little longer.
妳就讓我再多做一下美夢嘛
I was not expecting the thief to steal the ring.
沒想到盜賊連重要的戒指都搶走了
We really can't make up for this sin.
我們實在無法彌補這個罪過
You both have already put in a lot of effort.
妳們兩個已經很努力了
Do not be so hard on yourself.
不要這麼自責
Appreciate your understanding.
謝謝您的諒解
That ring comes with a condition.
那枚戒指有一個規定
As a reward
打倒魔王的勇者
for beating the Devil King,
作為獎勵
the hero can marry the princess.
能得到娶王女為妻的權利
Brother…
哥哥…
I hope he will cherish the ring.
希望他能好好珍惜戒指
The sacred treasure…
神器…
You mean that the thief not only took my sacred treasure
我的神器不只被盜賊偷走
but also sealed it?
還被封印了
Get it back!
快給我找回來
That's impossible.
那是不可能的
I did not expect the sacred treasure to be sealed.
沒想到神器會被封印
I have already used up all my options.
我已經無計可施了
You useless fellow!
你這個沒用的傢伙
When exactly will you make
你究竟要到什麼時候
my wish come true?
才能實現我的願望
(Episode 7: Rest in Peace, The Upstart Adventurer)
(第7集 為一步登天的冒險者 獻上安息)
I am Sylvia.
我是您的席薇亞
I have completely gotten used to vacationing.
我已經徹底習慣度假了
This feeling of freedom
這種解脫感
is good.
充實
A powerful woman…
女強人…